

Personal profile

# **Dimitri Lyomin**

Front-End developer

₱ Penza, Russia

I'm a Front-End developer with 5+ years of experience. I create, develop and maintain websites from plain markups to high-loaded, scalable and performant SPA. I'm responsible, reliable, flexible and well-organized. I work well with others and I value and respect time constraints and deadlines. I am also great with clients: when a client has a question, I take the time to explain and clarify our process to them in an appropriate way.

### **Professional experience**

### Front-End Developer @EastWood, Penza, Russia

March 2015 - Present

- Developed, maintained and improved SPA working with Transparency.js
- Created and implemented use of Unit Tests with Karma and Jasmine
- Built mobile version application
- Improved rendering time characteristics of application
- · Middle management, assigned tasks among team
- Code review
- Developed and improved custom architecture SPA created with native JS

### Front-End Developer @Q-Cis, Moscow, Russia

February 2014 – February 2015

- Built responsive and adaptive websites
- Developed, maintained and improved SPA based on AngularJS
- Created markup application with LESS and Bootstrap

### Front-End Developer @Crowd Lab, Moscow, Russia

March 2013 - September 2013

- Built responsive and adaptive websites
- Developed, maintained and improved SPA with AngularJS
- Developed and improved markup application with Stylus

### Front-End Developer / Back-End Developer @Freelance, Moscow, Russia / Kiev, Ukraine

October 2012 - February 2013

- Built responsive and adaptive websites
- Maintained and improved back end with php

### Front-End Developer @Popel Studio, Kiev, Ukraine

September 2011 – September 2012

- Built and improved custom websites with Joomla, Wordpress, Kohana
- Maintained and improved back end with php

## Personal projects

• Created and developed time-tracking SPA with Backbone.js (chronacc.com)



2 lyomin.com





https://github.com/lemind

### **Expertise & Core Skills**

### **Development**

- JavaScript, HTML
- · CSS (LESS, Stylus), BEM, Bootstrap
- ¡Query

#### Workflow

- Git
- · WebPack, Gulp
- · Testing: Karma, Jasmine

#### Basic Knowledge

 Angular2, TypeScript, Reactive-Extensions

### **Frameworks**

• Angular, Backbone.js, Transparency.js

### **Project Management**

- · Agile, Jira, Remote Working Back-End
- · Nodejs, Express, PHP, MySQL

### Education

### **Bachelor of Computer Science** @Penza State University

2001-2006

Specialization in Engineering: Automatic System of Information Processing and Managing

### Languages

Russian - Native English — Intermediate